Welcome friends to your own YouTube
channel Surat Boy Krishna, so friends
everyone books tickets, according to me
everyone must be taking travel insurance, 0.4
notice army 49 paise tax, everyone must be
taking travel insurance, so friends today
in this video I will tell you
how important 49 paise is for you, if you
slate that option while booking a ticket
and choose railway at 0.49 pitch, then
friends if seen from the fund, then
eighty percent people or 90%
travel on 2014 notice, many
people do not do all this, so the excise duty is on those who
want to do it, now friends I
want to tell you how important is Jio phone ₹40
for you, so friends first of all
I want to tell you if
you must have seen that most of the people
get insurance from Shri Ram General
Insurance Company and then
apart from one Bharti, most of them get it from Shri Ram
General Insurance Company, so
friends they have retirement conditions and first of all
I want to tell you that
whenever you do these fixed insurance, if you
take insurance in it, then you must share all the details in it.
Now a thought comes to your mind
and what are minerals, so
friends, the details are that
if by chance you lose something, God forbid,
if anything X Y Z happens to you during the train journey, then who will
get the money, so friends,
you will have to play a limited game, in nominated
S, you will have to enter the name, father's
murder, accident, they give a lot of options,
now I want to tell you how to do the nominal fee,
you
can do it in two ways, one you will go to the website,
go to My Booking on the IRCTC website, then
there you will simply type in the company of travel
insurance, then
you will be asked to enter your PNR
number etc., after that friends you will have to
enter the email ID, after that
you will simply get a notification that means the name of the person whose name you
enter, what is your father's,
murder's, the system will open, after that send it, then
you will receive it on your Gmail ID, that
means which benefits you are going to get
and related to rice will be provided
to your Gmail ID by Shri Ram General,
so friends,
please write it below, most of the people make this mistake, they
book the ticket  Let's do that, we do
n't feel no office, nominated friends,
if you don't feel, there is no point in doing anything in 0.49, that's why
I keep
telling you again and again, please share that tweet
and secondly, friends, whenever you book a ticket at
home, if you leave from Delhi, if you go
through someone, then this
insurance option also comes to your mail, you
can update the date from there, say normal,
sweet, if you don't feel it, then you will
not get the benefit, now friends, I
want to tell you, if any
accident happens to you, then how Shri Ram will
quickly tell you the safety news,
during the journey, if due to any reason, friends,
during your trip to Britain, if you meet with a date, if
you meet with a train accident, then 10 lakh
rupees will be given to you by Shri Ram General Sense,
whereas if
during the journey, if the train meets with an accident,
due to any reason, your hands and legs get injured, that is,
your under eyes get injured,
in that case, all the alarms will be given seven and a half lakh rupees,
if a
train accident happens during the journey,
you want to take care of minor
matters.  They keep on doing this, if you are
admitted in the hospital, the expenses up to Rs 2 lakh will be borne by the
organizer Shri Ram &
Sons. So friends, this is the facility of Shri Ram
General Insurance, so much
facility is provided to you. Now a
thought must be coming in your mind that Sir, I have travelled many times and spent
Rs 0.49 but something like this never happens. So
friends, pray to God that the team never meets with an
accident. However, when you
book e-ticket, pack this. Although
going near small stations is a
different matter, but still you will see that the
security of the railways has become very tight.
Accidents have started decreasing a lot. They are becoming almost
negligible. But still, you should look at the 0.49 beauty
or not look at the money. If you offer that much,
friends, it will be better.
Today a thought must be coming in your mind, Sir, this is
providing insurance. The profit of the railways in the film is one
and a half. What profit do the railways make to us, sister,
if some accidents happen, then
friends, I want to tell you one thing,
if there was a real accident, then the railways would
also have some responsibility in it.  The
situation is that whatever treatment
you will have to pay, the insurance company will
pay for it and you have not taken any insurance, although the
railways will also pay for it and the railways will
take the full profit of it. Profit means that the railways will
give you it, it is up to the railways that if your debt is
such, whether they give compensation or
not depends on the railways. If
you have taken insurance from Shri Ram
Channel, Mission Resistance Party, XYZ,
any company, then they have different
tanks and fasts, then take their Duncan
Sherpa, go to their website and talk to their care,
then they will tell you
which benefits you will get, although the
railways will also give you profit, if you have
not taken it, then friends, I
want to tell you more about this thing, suppose
you are travelling in a train, you have
taken insurance, but due to some
disease,
your passenger suddenly dies, then in
that situation, friends, if you have
taken insurance from any company, then
friends, you cannot make any claim,
you will not be given any profit from their side
because this is the reason, friends, if the
train  If you suffer an accident, then
those companies will work at this time. If you
die suddenly due to any illness, then
no company is going to help you in this matter.
However, whatever help you will get from the Railways, the
Railways will definitely help you hundred percent, at
zero percent charge. But friends,
I want to make it clear to you that whatever the Railways does at a fixed
price,
everything is included in it, so the Railways is going to
provide you everything. So friends, that is why
I was starting the video. Now,
before going into the details, I want to tell you that
whenever you book a ticket, do
take insurance. Friends, taking insurance is very
beneficial. Now, a thought must be coming to your mind.
Sir, you have told about online, now that
line is drawn off. Therefore, if we
take out a ticket offline, this
facility is provided to us. Let me
tell you at one place, the reservation form does
not have the option of travel insurance anywhere in it. If you will see the rice,
friends,
you must take a ticket at a counter on the link. The ticket guy, who is the
ticket officer, will then do your
travel insurance in an easy way. Yes friends, with all this,
this
facility is available from both the places.  It is done,
however, if we talk to Mr. Ramcharan Sone,
he says that
this has been provided to us by IRCTC, it has been provided to
us only through the online website, the
insurance
facility is also available in the flight, you will have to
go there and ask for it, although
most of the people do not pay attention to all these things while applying,
but if you want safety, you will have to do it there, so
thanks for watching
friends, I hope you found today's video
quite difficult, so you
can definitely subscribe for similar videos like Pani Liya Surat Vacation